firehost.com 2019-07-05

# Privacy Statement - Armor

Effective Date: 1/15/2019

Armor Defense Inc., (“Armor” or “we” or “us” or “our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers (“customers” or “you”).  This Privacy Statement describes how we collect, utilize, distribute and protect personally identifiable information you provide to us through our website: www.armor.com and our service platform. It also describes the choices available to you regarding Armor’s use of your personally identifying information and the steps you can take to access, update and correct your personal information. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Armor.

For the purposes of this Privacy Statement, “customer” shall mean any past, present, or prospective user of Armor’s products or services, including any users of the Armor Website (the “Site”).

**EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield**

Armor has offices in the United States and the United Kingdom.  Therefore, it is possible that your information may be available to these offices.  To ensure adequate protection of the transfer of your personal information to these jurisdictions, Armor participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework.  We are committed to subjecting all personal information received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland to the Framework’s applicable Principles. Armor is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield Frameworks, and to view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List. [ **[https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/)** ]

Armor is responsible for the processing of personal information it receives under the Privacy Shield Framework, and may subsequently provide personal information to third parties to perform services on our behalf.  Armor complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.  That is, if we transfer personal information received under the Privacy Shield to a third party, Armor will obtain assurances from the third party that they will safeguard personal information in a manner consistent with our obligations under the Privacy Shield. We will remain responsible under the Privacy Shield for any failure to do so by the third party, unless we prove we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

Armor ’s adherence to the Privacy Shield may be limited in circumstances where Armor may be required to disclose personal information such as in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security, public interest or law enforcement requirements, or as required by statute, government regulation, or court order.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at  **<https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>**.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website [ **<https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>** ], you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

**Personally Identifiable Information We Collect   ****Information Provided by You**

Armor receives and stores any information you provide to us through your use of our Site, the Armor products or services, including correspondence relating to customer support, or in any other manner. Such information includes, but is not limited to, contact details such as your first and last name, telephone number(s), physical addresses, mailing address, job title, email address, and log-in credentials (as applicable). You may choose not to provide certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of many of our features.

**Financial Information:  **Customers may be required to submit financial information such as first and last name, credit card number and billing address in order to receive certain services from Armor. Armor will not sell, share or rent any of your financial information, except as set forth in this Privacy Statement or as necessary to provide the services.

**Automatic Information:**  Armor may collect and store certain information about your visits and interactions with our site that does not directly identify you, but is automatically received and recorded by us through use of “cookies.” We use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user-base. You can control the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. If you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

Additionally, as is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you.  We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.

**For information Collected through our Service Platform:** Armor collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal information it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Armor’s Client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients.

We will retain personal information we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Armor will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Social Media Widgets:  **The Site includes social media features, such as the Facebook button and other widgets or interactive mini-programs that operate on our Site. These features may collect information such as your IP address, which page(s) you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing the applicable feature.

**Behavioral Targeting/Re-Targeting** :  We partner with a third-party ad network to either display advertising on our Site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish not to have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking  **[here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/)**  (or if located in the European Union  **[click here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)** ). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

However, even where a customer has opted out of receiving any marketing data, in order to fulfill our service obligations, Armor will continue to send emails regarding customers’ account administration or interruptions to the Services for system maintenance.

**E-mail Communications:**  Electronic communications may be sent by Armor using customers’ personal contact information to provide information related to product offerings, important industry news or general services and upgrades provided by Armor. Armor may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from Armor.com if your computer supports such capabilities. Under no circumstances will we use this information for anything else not described in this Privacy Statement. All users may at any time opt-out of our marketing by clicking the Unsubscribe link located at the bottom of all marketing and customer notices or by submitting a General Inquiry at  **[https://www.armor.com/contact-us](https://www.armor.com/contact-us/)**.   However, in order to fulfill our service obligations, Armor will continue to send emails regarding customers’ account administration or service interruptions for system maintenance.

**Information from Other Sources** : We may collect information from other sources such as lead generating third party companies to correlate the information to your already submitted information. We do not do verifications on individuals’ personal information. All verification is at the business level, not the individual level.

**How We Use Personal Information**

Armor may collect information about you through your use of the Site or use of Armor products and services for several reasons, including:

  * to carry out obligations arising under agreements entered between you and Armor for products or services;
  * for research regarding the effectiveness of the Site and related marketing, advertising and sales efforts;
  * to respond to your service related requests and to communicate with you;
  * to provide you with information about Armor products and services for which you utilize or for which you have inquired;
  * to contact you regarding products and services offered by Armor and its trusted affiliates, business partners, and independent contractors; or;
  * to investigate, prevent, or act regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Armor’s Terms of Services Agreement or Acceptable Use Policy, or as otherwise required by law.

**How We Share Personal Information**

We may share personal information with business partners, service vendors, authorized third-party agents or contractors (such as Google, Inc. or Adobe Systems Inc.) in order to provide the services.

Information collected from customers may be disclosed to independent contractors and business

partners who have agreed (i) to hold this information in confidence, (ii) not to use it for any purpose except to carry out the service they are providing on behalf of Armor, and (iii) only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Statement and security policies in the way this information is handled. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

Armor may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from customers to actual or prospective investors and partners. Should a sale of Armor’s business ever occur, collected customer information may be transferred along with the sale but the information will be treated in the same manner as set forth in this Privacy Statement. In the event of any significant changes to the manner your information is handled, we would notify you by a prominent notice on the Site.

We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process by disclosing your personal information and other related information, to the extent necessary.

**Sites other than Armor:**  While visiting Armor’s website you may be directed to content or functionality that is hosted by a third-party. When information is collected by these third parties exclusively on Armor’s behalf, Armor’s Privacy Statement govern how information is used. The Site may contain links to third-party websites. Please note that these websites’ privacy and other policies may differ from those of Armor. We strongly recommend that you review the privacy policies of any online service prior to submitting personally identifiable information. Armor has no control over and is not responsible for the information practices of other websites, including those to which we may link and those which may link to us.

**Data Integrity and Security**

Armor makes diligent efforts to maintain accurate information on our customers. Armor has put stringent security procedures in place to protect such information collected about our customers. We constantly monitor our systems, which are protected using industry-standard security measures. Transport Layer Security (“TLS”) connections are used to communicate to our system to protect customer financial information (such as credit card number or bank account information), as well as encrypting vital information that customers input through the Site. Although reasonable efforts are made to secure network communications and the Site, Armor cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at  **[privacy@armor.com](mailto:privacy@armor.com)**.

**Accessing/Updating/Correcting/Deleting/Transferring or Handling of your Personally Identifiable Information**

At any time, you can request access to your personal information, request that any inaccuracies be corrected, and request that comments or explanations be added to records about you, by contacting  **[us](mailto:legal@armor.com)**. You can also ask about:

  * whether and why we have your personal information;
  * how we got your personal information;
  * what we have done with your personal information;
  * to whom we have communicated your personal information;
  * where your personal information has been stored, processed or transferred;
  * how long we will retain your personal information, or how that retention period will be determined; and
  * the safeguards in place to protect your information when it is transferred to third parties or third countries.

Finally, you can ask us not to collect or use your personal information for certain purposes, you can ask us to delete your personal information, or you can ask us to provide your personal information to a third party.

Depending on which laws apply to your personal information, we may only be able to do some of these things for you. If you request one of these things and we refuse to do it, we will explain your legal rights, the reason for our refusal and any recourse you may have.  We will respond to your request without undue delay within 30 days.  Armor reserves the right to take reasonable steps to verify customer identity prior to granting access or processing changes or corrections.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services and to fulfill the purposes for which the data was collected.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information on our Site from those we actually know are under the age of 16, and no part of our Site is structured to attract anyone under 16.

**Conditions of Use, Concerns**

By choosing to visit and interact with Armor, customers agree that their visit and any dispute regarding the protection of their privacy during such visit is subject to this Privacy Statement including, but not limited to, the provisions regarding limitations on damages and the application of the law of the state of Delaware.

Please note that if customers enter into other contractual agreements with Armor, privacy terms and conditions of such other agreements may supplement or supersede this statement. Questions and concerns about privacy at Armor should be directed to  **[privacy@armor.com](mailto:privacy@armor.com)**.

By Mail: Armor Defense Inc.  
2360 Campbell Creek Blvd., Suite 525  
Richardson, Texas 75082  
+1 (877) 262-3473

Attn: Data Protection Officer

**Revisions or Changes**

Armor reserves the right to modify this Privacy Statement from time to time. If we propose to make any material changes, we will notify you by means of a notice on this page prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
